

Mangukiya Hardik

Auckland, NZ • (022)5332568 • hdmangukiya3@gmail.com• hdmangukiya.github.io/

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Trained designing and developing software for business solutions

Self-managed developer who likes to investigate and accept challenges and whose work experience is focused mostly on developing side front0end and Back-end. I would like to be one of key developers in a strong proactive "continuous delivery"-aware development team working on a project that will require the team to make long-term architectural decisions and master new frameworks.

Key skills Experienced with:

• Languages: C#, .Net, Web Services, LINQ, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, HTML-CSS

• Applications: MS Visual Studio, MSMS

• Application servers: IIS, XAMP

• Operating systems: Windows, MAC

• Database systems: SQL Server, MySQL

• Certifications: IC Agile Certified

Key skills Knowledge with:

• Languages: PHP, Angular, NodeJS, HTML5

• Applications: PhpMyAdmin, WORDPRESS

• Application servers: GIT, WAMP

• Operating systems: Linux

Database systems: MongoDB, MySQL

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Total IT Solution, Auckland.

Technician - Intern (APR 2019— JUNE 2019)

Part of the Total IT Solution Technician team.

Responsible for:

- Maintain websites and Update every week.
- Understand customer queries, Maintain and support hardware to the customer.
- Processed, sorted, fixed, repaired, and imaged countless computers.
- Data Backup for Damaged HDD.
- Setup monitoring and managing customized catalogs, reporting.
- Everyday CRM and Inventory update.

Differenz System.

JR. SOFTWARE Developer (Apr 2017— Jun 2017)

Backend Software in Differenz System Team.

Responsible for:

Receiving product feature specification and creating design documents and test plan.

- Follow Agile and Lean Methodology with scrum meetings.
- Designed normalize database associated with stored procedure in SQL Server.
- I have developed Webpages and Stored procedures using Asp.net MVC and SQL Server.
- I have created WebAPIs to support mobile application development.
- Developed and maintained projects on version control system on subversion SVN.
- I have worked with using the object-oriented programming concept.

Elaunch Infotech, Surat, India.

Intern & Jr. Software Developer (Sep 2016—March 2017)

Participated in intensive, three-month Internship for Project management and Software development training program.

Responsible for:

- I have Learned and developed web-based software using a computer programming language such as Asp.net, C# and SQL Server with MVC framework.
- Worked with Agile software development team and Participate meeting for upcoming sprint discussion and progress work.
- I was creating and maintaining Asp.net based Websites and their Web Applications as per the initial guidelines of clients and Team Leaders.
- I am making changes to existing web applications according to feedback received from end-user or tester.
- Perform Unit testing of Web Application on different browsers and check all functionalities as per requirement.

EDUCATION & CREDENTIALS

Unitec Institute of Technology, Auckland, NZ Graduate Diploma in Computing, 2018-19

Babaria Institute of Technology, Gujarat, IND Computer Science and Engineering, 2012-16

REFERENCES

Available on Request.